[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company created the worlds largest doughnut in 1998?", "correct_answer": "Winchells House of Doughnuts", "incorrect_answers": ["Dunkin Doughnuts", "Grannys Doughnuts", "Krispy Kreme"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Towards the beginning of the new millennium, three of these four countries had a population of approximately 32 million people. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Colombia", "incorrect_answers": ["Algeria", "Kenya", "Morocco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the Mexican bandito, Calvera in the film The Magnificent Seven?", "correct_answer": "Eli Wallach", "incorrect_answers": ["Ricardo Montalban", "Antonio Banderas", "Edward James Olmos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a species of reindeer?", "correct_answer": "Northern caribou", "incorrect_answers": ["Woodland carribou", "Arctic reindeer", "Mountain reindeer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Classical composer Chopin had a lover named George.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country of the UK was Dunlop cheese created?", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Ireland", "Wales"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This garment, which replaced the corset, is constructed of elasticized fabric and usually fastened by hook and eye closures.", "correct_answer": "Girdle", "incorrect_answers": ["Brassiere", "Camisole", "Boxers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This oceanic dolphin has distinctive yellow patches on its sides. It is mostly found in the northern latitudes of the Atlantic Ocean.", "correct_answer": "Atlantic white-sided dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["Hector\u2019s dolphin", "Atlantic yellow-sided dolphin", "Common dolphin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does WWW stand for?", "correct_answer": "World Wide Web", "incorrect_answers": ["Wild Wonderful World", "Whole World Web", "World War Web"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie, shot in Ontario, is about 4 high schoolers and their attempts to see KISS in concert.", "correct_answer": "Detroit Rock City", "incorrect_answers": ["Not Another Teen Movie", "Better Than Chocolate", "Ghost World"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the diamond linked with a spring month?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1953, this New Zealander developed the technique of continuous fermentation, which is applied in the production of the famous beer brand Guinness.", "correct_answer": "Morton W. Coutts", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Mopps", "James Death", "Daniel Wheeler"]}]